var categories = [
  {
    index: 0,
    name: "GENDER COMMUNICATION STYLES",
    questions: [
      {
        index: 1,
        category: 0,
        value: '$100',
        question: "Aware to nonverbal cues, this sex is the more intuitive of the two.",
        answer: "What are Women?"
      },
      {
        index: 2,
        category: 0,
        value: '$200',
        question: "This gender works through problems internally.",
        answer: "What are Men?"
      },
      {
        index: 3,
        category: 0,
        value: '$300',
        question: "The gender that uses hierarchical leadership methods, includes only those within their level on decision making when necessary.",
        answer: "What is masculine leadership style?"
      },
      {
        index: 4,
        category: 0,
        value: '$400',
        question: "Building relationships while working on a task suits this sex the best.",
        answer: "What are Men?"
      },
      {
        index: 5,
        category: 0,
        value: '$500',
        question: "More comfortable asking for help, this sex can assign tasks to others with ease.",
        answer: "What are Women in leadership?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    index: 1,
    name: "THROUGH THE GENERATIONS",
    questions: [
      {
        index: 1,
        category: 1,
        value: '$100',
        question: "Stability is the aim of this generation’s game.",
        answer: "What is Generation X?"
      },
      {
        index: 2,
        category: 1,
        value: '$200',
        question: "This generation identifies with their work.",
        answer: "Who are the Baby Boomers?"
      },
      {
        index: 3,
        category: 1,
        double: true,
        value: '$300',
        question: "The ability to collaborate with others is important to which of the generations?",
        answer: "Who are the Baby Boomers and Millennials"
      },
      {
        index: 4,
        category: 1,
        value: '$400',
        question: "Individuality is important within the work place.",
        answer: "Who are Millennials?"
      },
      {
        index: 5,
        category: 1,
        value: '$500',
        question: "Work and home balance capability within a career is a real concern when considering a career to them.",
        answer: "Who are Generation X and Millennials?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    index: 2,
    name: "CLASSY DIFFERENCES",
    questions: [
      {
        index: 1,
        category: 2,
        value: '$100',
        question: "The average adult knows 20,000 to 30,000 of these.",
        answer: "What are words?"
      },
      {
        index: 2,
        category: 2,
        value: '$200',
        question: "Snap perception based soley on demographic.",
        answer: "What is a stereotype? "
      },
      {
        index: 3,
        category: 2,
        value: '$300',
        question: "Typically, with more of this comes higher education.",
        answer: "What is money?"
      },
      {
        index: 4,
        category: 2,
        value: '$400',
        question: "Containing 171,476 segments this plays a big role in the United States’ communication.",
        answer: "What is the English Language?"
      },
      {
        index: 5,
        category: 2,
        value: '$500',
        question: "Common interest can be found in all of these.",
        answer: "What are all Social Classes?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    index: 3,
    name: "WHO IS LISTENING?",
    questions: [
      {
        index: 1,
        category: 3,
        value: '$100',
        question: "Alternating your style of speech to accommodate this person can lead to effective communication.",
        answer: "Who is your audience?"
      },
      {
        index: 2,
        category: 3,
        value: '$200',
        question: "When you push your own agenda above all else, this may get lost.",
        answer: "What is your message?"
      },
      {
        index: 3,
        category: 3,
        value: '$300',
        question: "A negative reaction due to poorly worded speaking habits.",
        answer: "What is taking offense?"
      },
      {
        index: 4,
        category: 3,
        value: '$400',
        question: "When we speak and our message is understood completely.",
        answer: "What is effective communication?"
      },
      {
        index: 5,
        double: true,
        category: 3,
        value: '$500',
        question: "When you cut out things you may be inclined to stay on a subject because of lack of interest or understanding in who is listening, It can be considered this style of speech.",
        answer: "What is Receiver Oriented Communication?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    index: 4,
    name: "WILD ABOUT COMMUNICATION",
    questions: [
      {
        index: 1,
        category: 4,
        value: '$100',
        question: "Lawyers and Doctors commonly confuse their customers and patients using this when communicating.",
        answer: "What is a broad vocabulary?"
      },
      {
        index: 2,
        category: 4,
        value: '$200',
        question: "They often internalize conflict within the workplace sometimes causing poor communication.",
        answer: "Who are Generation X?"
      },
      {
        index: 3,
        category: 4,
        value: '$300',
        question: "We use this as a tool to express ourselves and collaborate with other humans.",
        answer: "What is communication?"
      },
      {
        index: 4,
        category: 4,
        value: '$400',
        question: "Some communication tendencies are biologically ingrained depending on this.",
        answer: "What is gender?"
      },
      {
        index: 5,
        category: 4,
        value: '$500',
        question: "The less literal of the two genders, they may use these motions to express they are listening.",
        answer: "What are nonverbal cues used by women? "
      }
    ]
  }
]

export default categories;
